本字幕由天满宫字幕组制作，翻译:neko，字幕:neko 校对:neko，cinewamage，请在下载后24小时内删除，若因私自传播造成的法律责任，字幕君概不负责。
My name is Van. I'm an artist. I'm a performance artist. I'm hired for people to fulfill their
我的名字是范。我是一名艺术家。我是一名表演艺术家。我被人雇佣来实现他们的幻想，
fantasies, their deep, dark fantasies. I was gonna be a movie star, you know, with modeling
他们深邃黑暗的幻想。我本来想成为一名电影明星，你知道，做模特和演员。
and acting. After a hundred or two auditions and small parts, you know, I decided, you
经过一百次或两百次试镜和小角色，你知道的，我认为，
know, I had enough. Then I get into escort work.
你知道的，我受够了。然后我开始从事陪同工作。
The clientele requested a lot of fetishes, so I just decided to go, you know, full
客户要求很多特殊癖好，所以我决定成为一个完整的主人，
master and change my whole entire house into a dungeon, um, dungeon master, you know, with
把整个房子改造成一个地牢，一个地牢主人，你知道的，
a full dungeon in my house, and it's going really well.
在我家里建立一个完整的地牢，而且进展得非常顺利。
Fisting is 300 bucks, and usually the guy is pretty much high on popper, to get really
拳交是300美元，通常这个人几乎总是在吸毒。所以你真的
get relaxed, you know, and I have this long latex glove that goes all the way up to my armpit
需要放松，我有一只长长的乳胶手套，一直延伸到我的腋窝。
And then I put on a surgical latex glove, just up to my wrist.
然后我戴上了一只手术用乳胶手套，刚好到我的手腕处。
And just lube it up and it's a long process, you know, to get your whole arm up there.
只需润滑一下，这是一个漫长的过程，你知道，要把整只手臂伸进去。
But it's an intense feeling for the other person.
但这对另一个人来说是一种强烈的感觉。
I think for myself too.
我自己也会这么想。
You go in places that even though it's physical with your hand,
你去到那些即使是用手触摸到的地方，
but for some reason it's also more emotional.
但出于某种原因，它也更具情感。
It's more psychological, too.
这也更多是心理上的。
And we both reach the same place.
我们俩都到达了同一个地方。
It's really strange at the same time.
这真的很奇怪。
And I found sessions like that, I get really exhausted at the end.
我发现那样的时间，我最后会感到非常疲惫。
I don't know, I feel kind of naked
我不知道，我感觉有点赤裸。
because I'm looking at myself for the first time, I think.
因为我第一次看到自己，
Well, not myself, but this aspect of my life for the first time and it's been gosh
我想。嗯，不是我自己，而是我生活的这个方面第一次，
Three to five years already. I never thought about it
已经过去了三到五年了。我从来没有想过这个
Kind of sad, I think I feel kind of sad right now. I don't know why
有点难过，我觉得我现在有点难过。我不知道为什么。